Guide to the Stanford University, Faculty Senate, Records SC0193
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Faculty Senate meetings [audio recordings], 1983-1993; Accession ARCH_1993_107
  - Senate XXI, 1989
    - Senate XXI (1 of 1), 1989 May 18; 2_7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2, Item 7)
    - Senate XXI (1 of 2), 1989 June 1; 2_8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2, Item 8)
    - Senate XXI (2 of 2), 1989 June 1; 2_9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2, Item 9)
    - Senate XXI (1 of 1), 1989 Jun 15; 2_10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2, Item 10)
    - Academic Senate, 1989 Sept 28; 2_11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2, Item 11)
    - Academic Senate (2 of 2), 1989 Sept 28; 2_12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2, Item 12)
    - Academic Senate, 1989 Oct 12; 2_13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2, Item 13)
    - Academic Senate (1 of 1), 1989 Nov 9; 2_14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2, Item 14)
    - Academic Senate (2 of 2), 1989 Nov 9; 2_15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2, Item 15)
    - Academic Senate (1 of 1), 1989 Nov 30; 2_16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2, Item 16)
    - Academic Senate (2 of 2), 1989 Nov 30; 2_17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2, Item 17)
  - Senate XXII, 1990
    Records dated: 2/8/90, 2/22/90, 4/5/90, 4/19/90, 5/3/90, 5/10/90, 5/17/90, 5/24/90, 5/31/90, 6/14/90; Tapes for Senate XXIII: 9/29/90
    - Part II, 1990 Feb 8; 3_1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3, Item 1)
    - Part III, 1990 Feb 8; 3_2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3, Item 2)
    - Academic Senate Part I; Part II, 1990 Feb 22; 3_3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3, Item 3)
    - Academic Senate, 1990 Apr 5; 3_4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3, Item 4)
    - Academic Senate, 1990 Apr 19; 3_5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3, Item 5)
    - Academic Senate (1 of 2), 1990 May 3; 3_6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3, Item 6)
    - Academic Senate (2 of 2), 1990 May 3; 3_7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3, Item 7)
    - Academic Senate Part; Part II, 1990 May 10; 3_8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3, Item 8)
    - Senate Mtg. (1 of 2), 1990 May 17; 3_9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3, Item 9)
    - Senate Mtg. (2 of 2), 1990 May 17; 3_10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3, Item 10)
    - Academic Senate, 1990 May 24; 3_11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3, Item 11)
    - Academic Senate (1 of 2), 1990 May 31; 3_12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3, Item 12)
    - Academic Senate (2 of 2), 1990 May 31; 3_13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3, Item 13)
    - Academic Senate (1 of 1), 1990 Jun 14; 3_14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3, Item 14)
    - Academic Senate (2 of 2), 1990 Jun 14; 3_15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3, Item 15)
    - Back up #1, 3_16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3, Item 16)
    - Part I; Part II, 1990 Sept 27; 3_17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3, Item 17)
    - Part III, 1990 Sept 27; 3_18; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3, Item 18)
  - Senate XXIII, 1990-1991
    Records dated: 10/11/90, 10/25/90, 11/8/90, 11/29/90, 1/24/91, 2/7/91, 2/21/91, 3/7/91; Tapes for Senate XXIV: 9/26/91, 10/2/91
    - Academic Senate Part I; Part II, 1990 Oct 11; 4_1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4, Item 1)
    - Academic Senate Part III, 1990 Oct 11; 4_2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4, Item 2)
    - Fac. Senate (1 of 2), 1990 Oct 25; 4_3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4, Item 3)
    - Fac. Senate (2 of 2), 1990 Oct 25; 4_4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4, Item 4)
    - Academic Senate (1 of 2), 1990 Nov 8; 4_5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4, Item 5)
    - Academic Senate (2 of 2), 1990 Nov 8; 4_6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4, Item 6)
    - Academic Senate (1 of 2), 1990 Nov 29; 4_7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4, Item 7)
    - Academic Senate (2 of 2), 1990 Nov 29; 4_8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4, Item 8)
    - Academic Senate Part III; Part IV, 1991 Jan 24; 4_9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4, Item 9)
    - Tape #1, 1991 Feb 7; 4_10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4, Item 10)
    - Tape #2, 1991 Feb 7; 4_11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4, Item 11)
    - Academic Senate, 1991 Feb 21; 4_12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4, Item 12)
    - Senate XXIII, 1991 Mar 7; 4_13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4, Item 13)
    - 24th Senate (1 of 2), 1991 Sept 26; 4_14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4, Item 14)
    - 24th Senate (2 of 2), 1991 Sept 26; 4_15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4, Item 15)
    - Faculty Forum (1 of 2), 1991 Oct 2; 4_16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4, Item 16)
    - Faculty Forum (2 of 2), 1991 Oct 2; 4_17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4, Item 17)
  - Senate XXIV, 1991-1992
    Records dated: 10/3/91, 10/10/91, 10/24/91, 11/7/91, 11/21/91, 1/9/92, 1/23/92, 2/6/92
    - Fac. Senate Open Forum (1 of 2), 1991 Oct 3; 5_1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5, Item 1)
    - Fac. Senate Open Forum (2 of 2), 1991 Oct 3; 5_2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5, Item 2)
    - Fac. Sen. Special Session I; Fac. Sen. Special Session II, 1991 Oct 3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5, Item 3)
    - Fac. Sen. Special Session III; Fac. Sen. Special Session IV, 1991 Oct 3; 5_4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5, Item 4)
    - Fac. Sen.I; Fac. Sen. II, 1991 Oct 10; 5_5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5, Item 5)
    - Fac. Sen.III, 1991 Oct 10; 5_6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5, Item 6)
    - Senate Part I; Part II, 1991 Oct 24; 5_7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5, Item 7)
    - Senate Part III, 1991 Oct 24; 5_8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5, Item 8)
    - Fac Sen I; Fac Sen II, 1991 Nov 7; 5_9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5, Item 9)
    - Fac Sen III, 1991 Nov 7; 5_10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5, Item 10)
    - Senate (1 of 2), 1991 Nov 21; 5_11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5, Item 11)
    - Senate (1 of 2), 1991 Nov 21; 5_12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5, Item 12)
    - Senate (2 of 2), 1991 Oct 21; 5_12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5, Item 12)
    - Academic Senate (1 of 2), 1992 Jan 9; 5_13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5, Item 13)
    - Academic Senate (2 of 2), 1992 Jan 9; 5_14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5, Item 14)
    - Academic Senate (1 of 1), 1992 Jan 23; 5_15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5, Item 15)
    - Academic Senate (1 of 2), 1992 Feb 6; 5_16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5, Item 16)
    - Academic Senate (2 of 2), 1992 Feb 6; 5_17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5, Item 17)
  - Senate XXIV, 1992
    Records dated: 2/13/92, 2/20/92, 3/5/92, 4/2/92, 4/9/92, 4/30/92, 5/14/92, 5/28/92, 6/11/92; Tapes for Senate XXV: 10/8/92, 10/29/92
    - Academic Senate (1 of 2), 1992 Feb 13; 6_1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6, Item 1)
    - Academic Senate (2 of 2), 1992 Feb 13; 6_2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6, Item 2)
    - Academic Senate (1 of 1), 1992 Feb 20; 6_3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6, Item 3)
    - Academic Senate (1 of 2), 1992 Mar 5; 6_4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6, Item 4)
    - Academic Senate (2 of 2), 1992 Mar 5; 6_5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6, Item 5)
    - Academic Senate (1 of 1), 1992 Apr 2; 6_6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6, Item 6)
    - Fac Sen (1 of 2), 1992 Apr 9; 6_7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6, Item 7)
    - Fac Sen (2 of 2), 1992 Apr 9; 6_8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6, Item 8)
    - Senate Meeting (1 of 1), 1992 Apr 30; 6_9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6, Item 9)
    - Senate (1 of 2), 1992 May 14; 6_10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6, Item 10)
    - Senate (2 of 2), 1992 May 14; 6_11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6, Item 11)
    - Fac Sen (1 of 2), 1992 May 28; 6_12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6, Item 12)
    - Fac Sen (2 of 2), 1992 May 28; 6_13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6, Item 13)
    - Fac Sen (1 of 1), 1992 Jun 11; 6_14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6, Item 14)
    - Academic Senate (1 of 2), 1992 Oct 8; 6_15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6, Item 15)
    - Academic Senate (2 of 2), 1992 Oct 8; 6_16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6, Item 16)
    - Fac Sen (1 of 2), 1992 Oct 29; 6_17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6, Item 17)
    - Fac Sen (2 of 2), 1992 Oct 29; 6_18; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6, Item 18)
  - Senate XXV, 1992-1993
    Records dated: 12/3/92, 1/7/93, 1/21/93, 3/4/93, 4/8/93, 4/15/93, 4/29/93, 5/5/93, 5/13/93, 5/27/93, 6/3/93, 6/10/93
    - Fac Sen (1 of 1), 1992 Dec 3; 7_1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7, Item 1)
    - Fac Sen (1 of 2), 1993 Jan 7; 7_2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7, Item 2)
    - Fac Sen (2 of 2), 1993 Jan 7; 7_3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7, Item 3)
    - Fac Sen (1 of 2), 1993 Jan 21; 7_4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7, Item 4)
    - Fac Sen (2 of 2), 1993 Jan 21; 7_5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7, Item 5)
    - Fac Sen (1 of 1), 1993 Mar 4; 7_6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7, Item 6)
    - Fac Sen (1 of 1), 1993 Apr 8; 7_7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7, Item 7)
    - Senate (1 of 1), 1993 Apr 15; 7_8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7, Item 8)
    - Academic Senate (1 of 1), 1993 Apr 29; 7_9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7, Item 9)
    - S+C (1 of 1), 1993 May 5; 7_10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7, Item 10)
    - Academic Senate (1 of 2), 1993 May 13; 7_11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7, Item 11)
    - Academic Senate (2 of 2), 1993 May 13; 7_12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7, Item 12)
    - Fac Sen (1 of 2), 1993 May 27; 7_13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7, Item 13)
    - Fac Sen (2 of 2), 1993 May 27; 7_14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7, Item 14)
    - Senate Back-up (1 of 1), 1993 Jun 3; 7_15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7, Item 15)
    - Fac Sen (1 of 1), 1993 Jun 3; 7_16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7, Item 16)
    - Academic Senate (1 of 1), 1993 Jun 10; 7_17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7, Item 17)
  - Academic Council, 1983-1991
    Records dated: 1/11/90, 2/14/90, 2/22/90, 5/10/90, 10/26/90, 1/10/91; Tapes of Ad Hoc Committee on Senate Representation: 7/19/83, 7/27/83, 9/14/83, 9/20/83; Tapes of Committee on Committees on: UG-EDPs 2/17/83; SC-RHISP 2/12/85; Overseas Studies Oversight 1/29/87, [meeting] 2/12/87
    - Academic Council Part I; Part II, 1990 Jan 11; 8_1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8, Item 1)
    - Academic Council Part III, 1990 Jan 11; 8_2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8, Item 2)
    - Academic Council Tape 2, 1990 Feb 14; 8_3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8, Item 3)
    - Academic Council Part III, 1990 Feb 22; 8_4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8, Item 4)
    - Academic Council Part III, 1990 May 10; 8_5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8, Item 5)
    - Academic Council Part I; Part II, 1990 Oct 26; 8_6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8, Item 6)
    - Academic Council Part III, 1990 Oct 26; 8_7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8, Item 7)
    - Academic Council Part I; Part II, 1990 Jan 10; 8_8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8, Item 8)
    - CoC Special Meeting, 1983 Feb 17; 8_9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8, Item 9)
    - Ad hoc C-SR (1 of 2), 1983 Jul 19; 8_10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8, Item 10)
    - Ad hoc C-SR (2 of 2), 1983 Jul 19; 8_11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8, Item 11)
    - Ad hoc C-SR (1 of 1), 1983 Jul 27; 8_12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8, Item 12)
    - Ad hoc Comm on Sen Rep (1 of 1), 1983 Sept 14; 8_13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8, Item 13)
    - Ad hoc Comm on Sen Rep (1 of 1), 1983 Sept 20; 8_14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8, Item 14)
    - CoC on SC-RHISP (1 of 1), 1985 Feb 12; 8_15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8, Item 15)
    - CoC XIX (1 of 1), 1987 Jan 29; 8_16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8, Item 16)
    - CoC (1 of 1), 1987 Feb 12; 8_17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 8, Item 17)
  - Miscellaneous recordings, 1987-1989
    Committee on Committees on: [meeting] 3/12/87; UCLBD Restructuring (with J.N. Rosse) 4/9/87; Tapes of Ad Hoc Committees on: Minority issues 6/17/87; Rainbow Agenda Cte. 6/11/87, 7/1/87, 9/18/87; Senate Representation 3/28/88; Tapes of StC Meetings: 11/16/88, 2/28/89, 3/1/89, 3/15/89; Three unlabeled tapes
    - CoC Meeting (1 of 1), 1987 Mar 12; 9_1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 9, Item 1)
    - CoC XIX (1 of 1), 1987 Apr 9; 9_2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 9, Item 2)
    - Organization Mtg for Rainbow Agenda (1 of 2), 1987 Jun 11; 9_3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 9, Item 3)
    - Organization Mtg for Rainbow Agenda (2 of 2), 1987 Jun 11; 9_4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 9, Item 4)
    - Ad Hoc Comm on the Univ Common Minority Isseus (1 of 1), 1987 Jun 17; 9_5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 9, Item 5)
    - Short Passage from Mtg of Ad Hoc Comm (1 of 1), 1987 Jun 22; 9_6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 9, Item 6)
    - Rainbow Bldg 10 (1 of 4); Rainbow Bldg 10 (2 of 4), 1987 Jul 1; 9_7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 9, Item 7)
    - Ad Hoc Group on Rainbow Agenda - Last Meeting (1 of 1), 1987 Sept 18; 9_8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 9, Item 8)
    - Ad Hoc Group on Senate Represenation (1 of 1), 1988 Mar 28; 9_9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 9, Item 9)
    - Sec (1 of 1), 1988 Nov 16; 9_10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 9, Item 10)
    - Sec (1 of 1), 1989 Feb 28; 9_11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 9, Item 11)
    - Stc mtg (1 of 1), 1989 Mar 1; 9_12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 9, Item 12)
    - Stc (1 of 1), 1989 Mar 15; 9_13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 9, Item 13)
    - Second Senate Tape, 9_14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 9, Item 14)
    - Meeting re: weapons research, 9_15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 9, Item 15)
    - Unidentified, 9_16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 9, Item 16)
- Minutes and supporting documents from Senate meetings, committees, and panels, 1966-1978; Accession ARCH_2000_193 (Box 1, Box 12, Box 3, Box 2, Box 8, Box 7, Box 10, Box 9, Box 13, Box 4, Box 6, Box 5, Box 17, Box 16, Box 11, Box 14, Box 15)
- Committee on Graduate Study records, 1915-1949; Accession ARCH_2005_213
  These minutes primarily pertain to students' admission to candidacy for a graduate degree; other subjects include procedures, requirements, transmittal of theses to the library, fees, and fellowship appointments.
  - Committee on Graduate Study, minutes, 1915-16 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Graduate Study, minutes, 1917-18 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Graduate Study, minutes, 1919-21 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Graduate Study, miscellaneous correspondence, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Graduate Study, minutes, 1922-23 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Graduate Study, minutes, 1922 Nov 5 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Committee on Graduate Study, minutes, Nov. 5, 1922 and "Procedure in cases of candidates for advanced degrees... in the Food Research Institution"
  - Committee on Graduate Study, minutes, extra copies for, Oct. 25, 1917-June 15, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Graduate Study, minutes, 1924-25 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Graduate Study, minutes, 1926-May 1927 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Graduate Study, minutes, Oct. 1927-Nov. 1929 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Graduate Study, minutes, Dec. 5, 1929-June 18, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Graduate Study, minutes, Oct. 6, 1932-June 14, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Graduate Study, minutes, Oct. 4, 1934-Aug. 18, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Committee on Graduate Study, minutes, Oct. 1, 1936-Aug. 1, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Graduate Study, minutes, Sept. 28, 1939-June 11, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Graduate Study, minutes, Aug. 6, 1942-Aug. 21, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Graduate Study, minutes, Oct. 12, 1944-Sept. 25, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Graduate Study, minutes, Nov. 7, 1946-Nov. 22, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Graduate Study, degree list, Oct. 1948 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Graduate Study, committee members, 1948/49 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Graduate Study, minutes, index notes (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Faculty Senate meetings [audio recordings], 1966-1970; Accession ARCH_2007_147
  - Academic Senate, reel #1, 1966 May 31; 1_10; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 1)
  - Academic Senate, reel #2, 1966 May 31; 1_10; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 1)
  - Academic Senate, reel #4, 1966 May 31; 1_10; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 1)
  - Academic Council, reel #2, 1966 Jun 1; 1_13; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 1)
  - Academic Council, reel #3, 1966 Jun 1; 1_14; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 1)
  - Academic Council, reel #5, 1966 Jun 1; 1_15; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 1)
  - Academic Council meeting, 1970 Apr; 1_16; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 1)
- Faculty Senate records, 1978-1979; Accession ARCH_2007_299
  - 11th Senate Agenda and minutes, 1978-79 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 11th Senate documents (1 of 4), 1978-79 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 11th Senate documents (2 of 4), 1978-79 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 11th Senate documents (3 of 4), 1978-79 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 11th Senate documents (4 of 4), 1978-79 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 11th Senate Steering Committee minutes, 1978-79 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 11th Senate Steering Committee documents (1 of 3), 1978-79 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 11th Senate Steering Committee documents (2 of 3), 1978-79 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 11th Senate Steering Committee documents (3 of 3), 1978-79 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 11th Senate Committees: A - E, 1978-79 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 11th Senate Committees: F - I, 1978-79 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 11th Senate Committees: La [mostly Land and Building], 1978-79 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 11th Senate Committees: Li - P, 1978-79 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 11th Senate Committees: R, 1978-79 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 11th Senate Committees: S - UA, 1978-79 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 11th Senate Committees: Undergraduate Studies, 1978-79 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 11th Senate Committee on Committees, documents and minutes (1 of 4), 1978-79 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 11th Senate Committee on Committees, documents and minutes (2 of 4), 1978-79 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 11th Senate Committee on Committees, documents and minutes (3 of 4), 1978-79 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 11th Senate Committee on Committees, documents and minutes (4 of 4), 1978-79 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Faculty Senate records [computer files], 1994-2016
  The materials are restricted 20 years from date of creation.
  - 27th Senate, 1994-1995
  - 28th Senate, 1995-1996
  - 29th Senate, 1996-1997
  - 30th Senate, 1997-1998
  - 31st Senate, 1998-1999
  - 32nd Senate, 1999-2000
  - 33rd Senate, 2000-2001
  - 34th Senate, 2001-2002
  - 35th Senate, 2002-2003
  - 36th Senate, 2003-2004
  - 37th Senate, 2004-2005
  - 38th Senate, 2005-2006
  - 39th Senate, 2006-2007
  - 40th Senate, 2007-2008
  - 41st Senate, 2008-2009
  - 42nd Senate, 2009-2010
  - 43rd Senate, 2010-2011
  - 44th Senate, 2011-2012
  - 45th Senate, 2012-2013
  - 46th Senate, 2013-2014
  - 47th Senate, 2014-2015
  - 48th Senate, 2015-2016
- Committee records, 1949-2011; Accession ARCH_2014_115
  Restricted 20 years from date of creation.
  - Accreditation, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Committees, 1954-1969 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
  - Department and Degree Programs Report, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Overseas Studies Program Report, 1981-2003 (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
  - Theme Houses Report, 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
  - Graduate Housing Report, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Freshmen and Sophomore Report, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Language Center Report, 1997-2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Subcommittee on Residential Educaiton, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Subcommittee on Academic Calendar, 1982-1998 (Box 1, Folder 13-14)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Standards and Policies, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Standards and Policies, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Writing Advisory Report Board, 1995-2000 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Committee of Administrative Deans for Undergraduate Studies, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Area One, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Area One, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Area One, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Area One, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Area One, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Area One, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Area One, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Area One, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Revised Area One, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Area One Interim Review C/V 96, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Area One, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Area One, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Area One, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Area One, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Report Res-Ed 1997 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Report Res-Ed 1997 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1951-1954 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1949-1959 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1954-1957 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1955-1959 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1959-1961 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1972-1975 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1952-1981 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1984-1993 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Subcommittee - EIT, 1972-1977 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Subcommittee - EIT, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Subcommittee - EIT, 1968-1983 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Subcommittee - EIT, 1977-1982 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Subcommittee - EIT, 1969-1996 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Subcommittee - EIT, 1969-1996 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Scientific Computing and Computational Mathmatics (SCCM), 1987-2004 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Scientific Computing and Computational Mathmatics (SCCM), 1987-1989 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - African and African American Studies (AAAS), 1995-2005 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - African and African American Studies (AAAS), 1968-1994 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - African and African American Studies (AAAS), 1968-1994 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - African and African American Studies (AAAS) Solicitation Material, 1975-2000 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Archaeology, 2000-2005 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Final Report Graduate Academic Life, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Final Report Graduate Academic Life, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Final Report Graduate Academic Life, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Final Report Graduate Academic Life, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - 27th Senate Report No.9, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 27th Senate Report No.9, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Standards and Policies, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Standards and Policies, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Social Science History, 1998-2001 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Symbolic Systems, 2001-2008 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Symbolic Systems, 2001-2008 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Urban Studies, 1999-2008 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Urban Studies, 1985-1997 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - American Studies, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - American Studies, 2000-2003 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - American Studies, 1995-2000 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - American Studies, 1989-1995 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Report, Statistical Study of Curriculum, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Committee for the Review of Undergraduate Majors Part 1, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 15)